warisboring.com 2019-12-15

# WAR IS BORING PRIVACY POLICY | War Is Boring

Last Modified on September 28, 2015

**_Our Privacy Commitment_**

War is Boring, Ltd., Co. (“ ** _War is Boring_** ,” “ ** _we_** ,” “ ** _us_** ” or “ ** _our_** ”) is committed to respecting the privacy rights and concerns of all users of War is Boring’s website where this Privacy Policy is posted (the “ ** _Site_** ”) (we refer to the Site and the services made available by War is Boring, collectively, as the “ ** _War is Boring Features_** ”). As such, we have established and implemented this Privacy Policy to inform visitors to the Site and users of the War is Boring Features how we use and protect the information we collect through the Site and/or the War is Boring Features. By accessing the Site or using any of the War is Boring Features, you consent to War is Boring’s collection, use, storage, deletion and disclosure of information relating to you as set forth in this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy is effective as of the date set forth above and is only applicable to the Site and the War is Boring Features and not to any other website or mobile application that you may be able to access from the Site or the War is Boring Features which may have its own data collection and use practices and policies.

This policy answers the following questions:

  * What information do we collect about you and how do we use it?
  * Will we share your personal information with third parties?
  * What choices do you have about the collection and use of your personal information?
  * What security measures do we take to safeguard your personal information?

**_What information do we collect about you and how do we use it?_**  

**Types of Information We Collect**

Personal information means information that can be used to identify and contact you. You do not need to submit personal information to access the War is Boring Features generally. However, you may be required to submit personal information to access certain aspects of the Site and the War is Boring Features. We may collect non-personal information such as your browser type, when you accessed the Site and from what physical location you accessed the Site (including your Internet Protocol (IP) address).  However, to the extent that your IP addresses or similar identifiers are considered personal information by local law, we also treat these identifiers as personal information.  This non-personal information may be aggregated to measure the number of visits, average time spent, page views, and other statistics about users of the Site. We also may use this data to monitor the Site’s performance and to make the Site easier and more convenient to use.

We collect personal information when you subscribe to our newsletter; participate in feedback forms or surveys; post comments on the Site; or receive customer or technical support.

If you wish receive communications about new products, services, features, or enhancements to the War is Boring Features that may be of interest to you, we require you to provide your email address. To post comments on the Site, we require you to provide certain information, including your name, screen name and email address. Providing additional information beyond what is required, such as your photo or website URL, is entirely optional, but enables you to gain more from the War is Boring Features. By submitting personal information through the Site, you authorize War is Boring to share this personal information for the purposes identified herein and on the Site, such as responding to user inquiries processing transactions, distributing materials, and requesting feedback.

**Third Party Privacy Policies**

Through the War is Boring Features, you may be able to link to technology, software and services owned and controlled by third parties (“ ** _Third Party Features_** ”). You may be permitted or required to submit personal information to access Third Party Features. Such use of Third Party Features and submission of information through Third Party Features will be subject to such applicable third party’s Terms of Use/Service and Privacy Policy. You agree to look solely to the applicable third party and not to War is Boring to enforce your rights in relation thereto. When you have clicked on a third party logo or URL displayed on the Site or accessible through the War is Boring Features, which links you to any Third Party Features, our Terms of Use no longer applies and you must read the Terms of Use/Service and Privacy Policy of the third party to see how your personal information will be handled on their website.

**How We Use Your Personal Information**

The personal information you provide to us will allow us to communicate with you and provide the War is Boring Features to you, depending on the War is Boring Features for which you register. This includes alerting you of new services, features, or enhancements to the War is Boring Features; verifying your identity; handling your customer service questions or issues; requesting feedback; distributing newsletters; and notifying you of promotions, updates, or special offers that we think may interest you. We may also use your email address as part of the War is Boring Features in sending you messages about the War is Boring Features and other general announcements. We keep track of your interactions with us, including but not limited to your activity within the War is Boring Features. Except as set forth in this Privacy Policy, or unless we have your consent, we will not share your personal information with any person or entity other than those affiliated with the Company, entities acting on behalf of the Company, and relevant third parties such as those needed to collect and maintain our information collection servers and perform technology and related services.

We may use your personal information with non-personal information that we have collected in a manner such that the end-product does not personally identify you or any other user of the War is Boring Features. We may make your personal information non-personally identifiable by either combining it with information about other users (aggregating your personal information with information about other users), or by removing characteristics (such as your name or email address) that make the information personally identifiable. This process is known as de-personalizing your information. You grant us a royalty-free, worldwide, perpetual, irrevocable and fully transferable right and license to use your personal information in connection with the creation and development of analytical and statistical analysis tools relating to the use of the customer data we collect in providing the War is Boring Features (the “ ** _Analytical Data_** ”). We are expressly authorized to make any commercial use of the Analytical Data, including without limitation, sharing the Analytical Data with third parties, provided that we do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer from us any part of the Analytical Data that personally identifies any War is Boring Features users

**Residents of the European Economic Area (“EEA”)**

Bright Mountain Media works with merchants and users around the world, including in the EEA. If you are located in the EEA, you have certain rights under European law with respect to your personal data, including the right to request access to, correct, amend, delete, port to another service provider, or object to certain uses of your personal data. If you are a merchant, a partner, a visitor, a customer of Bright Mountain Media’s websites, please reach out to us using this email privacy@brightmountainmedia.com. Additionally, if you are located in the EEA, we are generally processing your information in order to fulfill contracts we might have to pursue the following legitimate interests, either for ourselves, our merchants, our partners, or other third parties:  
To provide merchants and others with our services;  
To prevent risk and fraud on our websites;  
To provide communications, marketing, and advertising;  
To provide reporting and analytics;  
To provide troubleshooting, support services, or to answer questions;  
To improve our services and websites.  
When we process personal information to pursue these legitimate interests, we do so where we believe the nature of the processing, the information being processed, and the technical and organizational measures employed to protect that information can help mitigate the risks to the data subject.

**Do Not Track**

In compliance with California legislation, AB370, effective January 1, 2014, War is Boring’s practices in responding to “do not track” signals and collecting user information over time and across a network of websites when you visit the Site are as follows: We do not honor the request of “do not track” signals sent by your browser when you visit the Site. Additionally, War is Boring may collect user information about your online activities over time and across different websites, or authorize third parties to do so.

**Google Analytics and Google Demographics and Interests Reports**

The Site uses Google Analytics and Google Demographics and Interests Reports to help us learn about who visits the Site and what pages are being viewed.

**Cookies**

“Cookies” are small bits of electronic information that a website sends to a visitor’s browser and are stored on the visitor’s hard drive. Like many websites, we employ cookies in certain areas of the Site to allow us to provide information to make your online experience more convenient. For example, cookies may enhance your experience of the War is Boring Features by tailoring content to you.

Third parties whose websites are accessible through links on the Site may also use their own cookies when you link to their site or service. War is Boring does not control these third parties’ use of cookies and cannot guarantee that they will uphold the same privacy standards as War is Boring. War is Boring expressly disclaims any and all liability related to the collection, use or disclosure of information by third parties. You should review the privacy policies of any third party sites that you visit through a link from the Site to understand how these third parties use cookies and the information they collect through cookies. Most cookies are “session cookies” which means that they are automatically deleted at the end of each session. Most browsers are initially set to accept cookies. You can set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie, giving you a chance to decide whether or not to accept it.

**Log Information**

Our servers automatically record information that your browser sends whenever you visit the Site. This information includes your IP address, your browser type and version, the search engine you used to find the War is Boring Features, if any, which War is Boring Features you use and from where, and when and how long you use them (the “ ** _Tracking Technology_** ”). We use this information to monitor and analyze how users use the War is Boring Features, to provide customer service and to maintain and improve the War is Boring Features.

**Children’s Privacy**

We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 13, or allow them to create an account for the War is Boring Features. We take children’s privacy seriously, and encourage parents to play an active role in their children’s online experience at all times.

**_Will we share your personal information with third parties?_**

**Sharing Your Information**

We use your personal information to provide the War is Boring Features to you, deliver products and services you request, handle your customer service questions or issues, send communications to you about promotions, updates, or special offers (which may be offered by War is Boring or one of its business partners) that may be of interest to you. The personal information uploaded by you through the War is Boring Features will be shared only with authorized persons you specifically grant access to. We may also use your personal information to provide analyses of our users in the aggregate (including Analytical Data subject to the terms of this Privacy Policy) to prospective partners and other third parties. We will also share the personal information we collect from you under the following circumstances:

  * _Protection of rights_. We will share personal information if we have a good faith belief that (i) access, use, preservation or disclosure of such information is reasonably necessary to satisfy any applicable law, regulation, legal process, such as a court order or subpoena, or a request by law enforcement or governmental authorities, (ii) such action is appropriate to enforce our Terms of Use for the War is Boring Features, including any investigation of potential violations thereof, (iii) such action is necessary to detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues associated with the War is Boring Features, or (iv) such action is appropriate to protect the rights, property or safety of War is Boring, its employees, users of the War is Boring Features or others.
  * _Asset transfers_. If we become involved in a merger, acquisition or other transaction involving the sale of some or all of War is Boring’s assets, user information, including personal information collected from you through your use of the War is Boring Features, could be included in the transferred assets. Should such an event occur, we will use reasonable means to notify you through email and/or a prominent notice on the Site.
  * _Service Providers_. We may share your personal information with service providers (including our affiliates that provide services on our behalf) that we engage for the purpose of processing information on our and your behalf. Additionally, we may partner with other companies to process, analyze, and/or store data, including, but not limited to, Analytical Data. While providing services for us, these companies may access your personal information. To the extent applicable, we require these entities to comply with this Privacy Policy and appropriate confidentiality and security measures.

**Additional Information You Should Know About Third Parties**

The Site may contain direct links to websites operated by our partners and other entities. These third party websites may collect information about you when you visit them or otherwise communicate with them. This Privacy Policy does not cover the information practices of third party websites linked to the Site or accessible through the War is Boring Features. Although we encourage such third parties to adopt and follow their own privacy policies, we are not responsible for their collection and use of your personal information. You should refer to the privacy policies and statements of other websites or contact the respective webmasters of those websites to obtain information regarding their information collection, use and disclosure policies.

When you have clicked on a third party logo or URL displayed on our Site or accessible through the War is Boring Features which links you to a different website, our Privacy Policy no longer applies and you must read the privacy policy of the third party to see how your personal information will be handled on their website.

**_What choices do you have about the collection and use of your personal information?_**

**Control of Your Information**

You may update or delete your personal information or modify your account preferences for the War is Boring Features by accessing the account interface provided through the War is Boring Features. Please note that if you disable your account, we will keep your contact information on file, and may retain other account information for a reasonable period of time afterward for the purpose of internal account management and fraud prevention activities.

**Opting Out of Receiving Communications From Us**

If you no longer want to receive our newsletter, emails or other announcements, you may unsubscribe by writing to us at privacy@warisboring.com or replying to the “unsubscribe” link at the bottom of our emails.

**Mediation**

You agree that, in the event any dispute or claim arises out of or relating to this Privacy Policy, you and War is Boring will attempt in good faith to negotiate a written resolution of the matter directly between the parties. You agree that if the matter remains unresolved for forty-five (45) days after notification (via certified mail or personal delivery) that a dispute exists, all parties shall join in mediation services in Columbia, South Carolina with a mutually agreed mediator in an attempt to resolve the dispute. Should you file any arbitration claims, or any administrative or legal actions without first having attempted to resolve the matter by mediation, then you agree that you will not be entitled to recover attorneys’ fees, even if you would otherwise be entitled to them.

**_What security measures do we take to safeguard your personal information?_**

The personal information that you provide to us is stored on servers, which are protected by protocols and procedures designed to ensure the security of such information. In addition, we restrict access to personal information to War is Boring employees, independent contractors and agents who need to know this information in order to develop, operate and maintain the War is Boring Features. However, no server, computer or communications network or system, or data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect user information, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us or through the use of any of the War is Boring Features and you acknowledge and agree that you provide such information and engage in such transmissions at your own risk. Once we receive a transmission from you, we will endeavor to maintain its security on our systems.

In the event that personal information you provide to us is compromised as a result of a breach of security, when appropriate we will take reasonable steps to investigate the situation, notify you and take the necessary steps to comply with any applicable laws and regulations.

**_Notification of Changes_**

This Privacy Policy may change from time to time and we will post all changes on the Site.

**_Questions? Contact Us_**

If you have any questions about our privacy practices or this Privacy Policy, please contact us by email at privacy@warisboring.com.

**_Terms of Use_**

Please read the Terms of Use governing the use of the Site and the War is Boring Features.
